{
    "topic": "Football",
    "Subject": "Sports",
    "data": [
        {
            "question": "Which Country is the winner of FIFA World Cup 204?",
            "op1": "Brazil",
            "op2": "Argentina",
            "op3": "Germany",
            "op4": "Netherlands",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the winner of Golden Ball award in the FIFA World Cup 014?",
            "op1": "Thomas Muller",
            "op2": "Lionel Messi",
            "op3": "Neymar Jr",
            "op4": "Ronaldo",
            "answer:": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the winner of the Silver Ball in the FIFA World Cup 2014?",
            "op1": "Miroslav Klose",
            "op2": "Arjen Robben",
            "op3": "Thomas Muller",
            "op4": "Mesut Ozil",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the winner of the Bronze Ball in the FIFA World Cup 201?",
            "op1": "Bastian Schweinsteiger",
            "op2": "Mesut Ozil",
            "op3": "Wesley Sneijder",
            "op4": "Arjen Robben",
            "answer:": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the winner of the Golden Boot in the FIFA World Cup 2014?",
            "op1": "James Rodr\u00edguez",
            "op2": "Fernando Torres",
            "op3": "David Villa",
            "op4": "Wayne Rooney",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the venue where the FIFA World Cup 2014 final match was played?",
            "op1": "Estadio das Dunas",
            "op2": "Estadio Do Maracana",
            "op3": "Arena Pantanal",
            "op4": "Arena de Sao Paulo",
            "answer:": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the winner of Golden Glove award in the FIFA World Cup 2014 ?",
            "op1": "Sergio Romario",
            "op2": "Karim enzema",
            "op3": "Manuel Neuer",
            "op4": "Lionel Messi",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of football in FIFA World Cup 2014?",
            "op1": "Telstar",
            "op2": "razuca",
            "op3": "Teamgeist",
            "op4": "Jabulani",
            "answer:": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country ranked in the third place in FIFA world cup 2014?",
            "op1": "Brazil",
            "op2": "Italy",
            "op3": "Netherlands",
            "op4": "France",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the winner of Hyundai Young Player award in FIFA World Cup 2014?",
            "op1": "Paul Pogba",
            "op2": "Wayne Rooneys",
            "op3": "David Villa",
            "op4": "Mario Balotelli",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Where the final match of the FIFA World Cup 2014 was played?",
            "op1": "Mineirao Stadium",
            "op2": "Maracan\u00e3 Stadium",
            "op3": "Arena de S\u00e3o Paulo",
            "op4": "Est\u00e1dio Nacional de Brasilia",
            "answer:": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who sang the theme song of FIFA World Cup 2014?",
            "op1": "Pitbull and Jennifer Lopez",
            "op2": "Kesha Rose Sebert",
            "op3": "Lady Gaga",
            "op4": "Enrique Iglesias",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How many goals scored in world cup 2014?",
            "op1": "160",
            "op2": "167",
            "op3": "171",
            "op4": "175",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who scored the highest individual goals in FIFA World Cup 20?",
            "op1": "james rodriguez",
            "op2": "Mesut Ozil",
            "op3": "Bastian Schweinsteiger",
            "op4": "Arjen Robben",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who scored the only goal in the final of FIFA World Cup 2014?",
            "op1": "Mario Gotze",
            "op2": "Fernando Torres",
            "op3": "David Villa",
            "op4": "Miroslav Klose",
            "answer:": 1
        }
    ]
}